A Guide to the James Whitcomb Riley Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #7133-v
James Whitcomb Riley Collection 188?-1916, n.d.
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
7133-v
11 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Purchase [1969] 1974 January 10
Item Listing
- Manuscripts
  - Poem, draft for obituary poem "Emerson", 1882 Apr 27; AMsS, 1 p.
  - Poem by Frank L. Stanton, "Lines Written by the man who was leaving", 1898 July 3; AMs initialed, 1 p.
  - Poem, draft for "A Happy Dream", [1916]; AMsS (xerox), 1 p.
  - Poem, draft for Raggedy Man, n.d.; AMs (thermaprint), 1 p.
- Letters
  - Henry van Dyke from Princeton to James Whitcomb Riley, [1901] Dec 12; ALS, 1 p. w/env
  - Henry van Dyke from Princeton to James Whitcomb Riley, 1903 Jan 14; ALS, 1 p. w/env
  - Henry van Dyke from Princeton to James Whitcomb Riley, 1904 Nov 17; ALS, 2 p. w/env
  - Henry van Dyke from Princeton to James Whitcomb Riley, 1906 Oct 20; ALS, 4 p. w/env
  - Henry van Dyke from Princeton to James Whitcomb Riley, 1906 Dec 21; AN, 1 p. w/env
  - Henry van Dyke from Princeton to James Whitcomb Riley, 1912 Feb 6; TLS, 2 p. w/env
- Miscellaneous
  - Newspaper clipping of "The Unwritten Song", 1898 May 31; Clipping